Lloyd: So now that you've
completed session two, it's time
to complete the relevant section
in the assessment booklet.
So if you open your assessment booklet
and scroll down to section two,
and you'll see that this is about
understanding procedures to maintain
data confidentiality and security.
And there are five
questions in this section.
Learning objectives are listed at the
top, where that is in the assessment
and where the information relating
to that is in the course materials
if you need to refer back to that.
So for question 1, it's asking you to
describe ways to protect stored data.
So for this question, you think about
the different ways that you've learned
about that you can use to protect the
stored data on a computer or a system.
Try and think of as many different
ways as possible to protect
that data in your response.
For question 2, it's asking
you to explain basic techniques
for encrypting information.
So again, using your learning
from the course materials, give an
explanation of the techniques that
you can use to encrypt information.
This then leads onto question 3, where
it's asking you to describe the advantages
and disadvantages of each encryption
technique, so what were the advantages and
disadvantage for each of those that you've
mentioned in your answer to question 2.
For question four, it's asking you to
define what is meant by the following:
data in transit, data at rest.
So you simply need to give a
definition of what that means.
So what is data in transit
and what is data at rest?
And then for question five, you
need to explain the security checks
an organization might undertake
before releasing information.
So what sort of checks
will they carry out?
What will they ask for?
What will they ask you to produce
before they would release information
to yourself or another person.
Once you've done that you
can then save the assessment
and move on to session three.